Kastle, Leonard; Papers ua902.021
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Operas, 1950-1988; Undated; 4; 12.7 cubic ft.
  - The Pariahs, 1950; 1961-1969; Undated; 4.3
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene IV Viola, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 10)
    - Blues of Parts, Act II Scene IV Violin 2, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 11)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scene I Bass, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 12)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scene I Bassoons 1 and 2, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 13)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scene I Bassoon 3 and Contra Bassoon, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 14)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scene I Cello, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 15)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scene I Clarinets 1-3 and Bass Clarinet, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 16)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scene I English Horn, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 17)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scene I Flutes 1 and 2 and Piccolo, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 18)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scene I Harps 1 and 2, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 19)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scene I Horns 1 and 2, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 20)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scene I Horns 3 and 4, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 21)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scene I Oboes 1-3, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 22)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scene I Percussion, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 23)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scene I Trombones 1 and 2, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 24)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scene I Trombone 3 and Tuba, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 25)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scene I Trumpets, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 26)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scene I Viola, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 27)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scene I Violin 2, Undated (Oversized 29, Folder 28)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scenes II and III Bass, Undated (Oversized 30, Folder 1)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scenes II and III Bassoons 1 and 2, Undated (Oversized 30, Folder 2)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scenes II and III Bassoon 3 and Contra Bassoon, Undated (Oversized 30, Folder 3)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scenes II and III Cello, Undated (Oversized 30, Folder 4)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scenes II and III Clarinets 1-3 and Bass Clarinet, Undated (Oversized 30, Folder 5)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scenes II and III English Horn, Undated (Oversized 30, Folder 6)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scenes II and III Flute and Piccolo, Undated (Oversized 30, Folder 7)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scenes II and III Harps 1 and 2, Undated (Oversized 30, Folder 8)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scenes II and III Horns 1 and 2, Undated (Oversized 30, Folder 9)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scenes II and III Horns 3 and 4, Undated (Oversized 30, Folder 10)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scenes II and III Oboes, Undated (Oversized 30, Folder 11)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scenes II and III Percussion, Undated (Oversized 30, Folder 12)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scenes II and III Trombones 1 and 2, Undated (Oversized 30, Folder 13)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scenes II and III Trombone 3 and Tuba, Undated (Oversized 30, Folder 14)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scenes II and III Trumpets, Undated (Oversized 30, Folder 15)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scenes II and III Viola, Undated (Oversized 30, Folder 16)
    - Blues of Parts, Act III Scenes II and III Violin 2, Undated (Oversized 30, Folder 17)
    - Blues of Parts, Epilogue Bass, Undated (Oversized 31, Folder 1)
    - Blues of Parts, Epilogue Bassoons 1-3 and Contra Bassoon, Undated (Oversized 31, Folder 2)
    - Blues of Parts, Epilogue Cello, Undated (Oversized 31, Folder 3)
    - Blues of Parts, Epilogue Clarinets and Bass Clarinets, Undated (Oversized 31, Folder 4)
    - Blues of Parts, Epilogue Flutes 1 and 2, Undated (Oversized 31, Folder 5)
    - Blues of Parts, Epilogue Harps, Undated (Oversized 31, Folder 6)
    - Blues of Parts, Epilogue Horns 1 and 2, Undated (Oversized 31, Folder 7)
    - Blues of Parts, Epilogue Horns 3 and 4, Undated (Oversized 31, Folder 8)
    - Blues of Parts, Epilogue Oboes 1-3 and English Horn, Undated (Oversized 31, Folder 9)
    - Blues of Parts, Epilogue Percussion, Undated (Oversized 31, Folder 10)
    - Blues of Parts, Epilogue Trombones 1 and 2, Undated (Oversized 31, Folder 11)
    - Blues of Parts, Epilogue Trombones 3 and Tuba, Undated (Oversized 31, Folder 12)
    - Blues of Parts, Epilogue Trumpets, Undated (Oversized 31, Folder 13)
    - Blues of Parts, Epilogue Viola, Undated (Oversized 31, Folder 14)
    - Blues of Parts, Epilogue Violin 1, Undated (Oversized 31, Folder 15)
    - Blues of Parts, Epilogue Violin 2, Undated (Oversized 31, Folder 16)
    - Blues of Piano-Vocal Score Prologue, Undated (Oversized 23, Folder 4)
    - Blues of Piano-Vocal Score Act I Scene I, Undated (Oversized 23, Folder 5)
    - Blues of Piano-Vocal Score Act I Scene II, Undated (Oversized 23, Folder 6)
    - Blues of Piano-Vocal Score Act I Scene III, Undated (Oversized 23, Folder 7)
    - Blues of Piano-Vocal Score Act I Scene VI, Undated (Oversized 23, Folder 8)
    - Blues of Piano-Vocal Score Act II Scene I, Undated (Oversized 23, Folder 9)
    - Blues of Piano-Vocal Score Act II Scene II, Undated (Oversized 24, Folder 1)
    - Blues of Piano-Vocal Score Act II Scene III, Undated (Oversized 24, Folder 2)
    - Blues of Piano-Vocal Score Act II Scene IV, Undated (Oversized 24, Folder 3)
    - Blues of Piano-Vocal Score Act III Scene I, Undated (Oversized 24, Folder 4)
    - Blues of Piano-Vocal Score Act III Scene II, Undated (Oversized 24, Folder 5)
    - Blues of Piano-Vocal Score Act III Scene III, Undated (Oversized 24, Folder 6)
    - Blues of Piano-Vocal Score Epilogue, Undated (Oversized 24, Folder 7)
    - Liberetto and Music, Undated (Box 6 (4-Operas), Folder 6)
    - Narration, Undated (Box 6 (4-Operas), Folder 7)
    - Orchestral Master Scores, Prologue - Epilogue, 1966 (Oversized 33)
    - Orchestral Score, Prologue - Act III, Undated (Oversized 18)
    - Original Liberetto, Prologue, ca. 1961 (Box 6 (4-Operas), Folder 8)
    - Original Liberetto, Act I, ca. 1961 (Box 6 (4-Operas), Folder 9)
    - Original Liberetto, Act II, ca. 1961 (Box 6 (4-Operas), Folder 10)
    - Original Liberetto, Act III and Epilogue, 1961 (Box 6 (4-Operas), Folder 11)
    - Original Piano-Voice Score, Prologue, 1950 (Oversized 22, Folder 1)
    - Original Piano-Voice Score, Act I Scene I, Undated (Oversized 22, Folder 2)
    - Original Piano-Voice Score, Act I Scene II, Undated (Oversized 22, Folder 3)
    - Original Piano-Voice Score, Act I Scene III, Undated (Oversized 22, Folder 4)
    - Original Piano-Voice Score, Act I Scene IV, 1967 (Oversized 22, Folder 5)
    - Original Piano-Voice Score, Act II Scene I, 1968 (Oversized 22, Folder 6)
    - Original Piano-Voice Score, Act II Scene II, 1968 (Oversized 22, Folder 7)
    - Original Piano-Voice Score, Act II Scene III, Undated (Oversized 22, Folder 8)
    - Original Piano-Voice Score, Act II Scene IV, 1968 (Oversized 22, Folder 9)
    - Original Piano-Voice Score, Act III Scene I, 1969 (Oversized 22, Folder 10)
    - Original Piano-Voice Score, Act III Scene II, 1969 (Oversized 23, Folder 1)
    - Original Piano-Voice Score, Act III Scene III, 1969 (Oversized 23, Folder 2)
    - Original Piano-Voice Score, Epilogue, 1969 (Oversized 23, Folder 3)
    - Piano-Vocal Score Act I, Undated (Oversized 41)
    - Piano-Vocal Score Act II, Undated (Oversized 41)
    - Piano-Vocal Score, Act I, Undated (Oversized 38, Folder 1)
    - Piano-Vocal Score, Act II, Undated (Oversized 38, Folder 2)
    - Piano-Vocal Score, Act III, Undated (Oversized 38, Folder 3)
    - Piano-Vocal Score, Act III, Undated (Oversized 39, Folder 1)
    - Piano-Vocal Score, Act II, Undated (Oversized 39, Folder 2)
    - Piano-Vocal Score, Act III, Undated (Oversized 39, Folder 3)
    - Piano-Vocal Score, Act II Scene II, Undated (Oversized 40, Folder 1)
    - Piano-Vocal Score, Act II Scene IV, Undated (Oversized 40, Folder 2)
    - Tissues of Orchestral Score, Prologue, 1966 (Oversized 32, Folder 1)
    - Tissues of Orchestral Score, Act I Scene I, 1966 (Oversized 32, Folder 2)
    - Tissues of Orchestral Score, Act I Scene II, 1966 (Oversized 32, Folder 3)
    - Tissues of Orchestral Score, Act I Scene III, 1966 (Oversized 32, Folder 4)
    - Tissues of Orchestral Score, Act I Scene IV, 1966 (Oversized 32, Folder 5)
    - Tissues of Orchestral Score, Act II Scene I, 1966 (Oversized 32, Folder 6)
    - Tissues of Orchestral Score, Act II Scene II, 1966 (Oversized 32, Folder 7)
    - Tissues of Orchestral Score, Act II Scene III, 1966 (Oversized 32, Folder 8)
    - Tissues of Orchestral Score, Act III Scene I, 1966 (Oversized 32, Folder 9)
    - Tissues of Orchestral Score, Act III Scene II, 1966 (Oversized 32, Folder 10)
    - Tissues of Orchestral Score, Act III Scene III and Epilogue, 1966 (Oversized 32, Folder 11)
    - Tissues of Parts, Prologue, Undated (Oversized 34, Folder 1)
    - Tissues of Parts, Prologue Bass Clarinet, Undated (Oversized 34, Folder 2)
    - Tissues of Parts, Prologue Bassoons, Undated (Oversized 34, Folder 3)
    - Tissues of Parts, Prologue Clarinet, Undated (Oversized 34, Folder 4)
    - Tissues of Parts, Prologue Contra Bassoon, Undated (Oversized 34, Folder 5)
    - Tissues of Parts, Prologue Horns 1 and 3, Undated (Oversized 34, Folder 6)
    - Tissues of Parts, Prologue Horns 2 and 4, Undated (Oversized 34, Folder 7)
    - Tissues of Parts, Prologue Percussion, Undated (Oversized 34, Folder 8)
    - Tissues of Parts, Prologue Piccolo, Undated (Oversized 34, Folder 9)
    - Tissues of Parts, Prologue Trombone 1 and 2, Undated (Oversized 34, Folder 10)
    - Tissues of Parts, Prologue Trombone 3 and Tuba, Undated (Oversized 34, Folder 11)
    - Tissues of Parts, Prologue Trumpet, Undated (Oversized 34, Folder 12)
    - Tissues of Parts, Prologue, Act I Scene I Bassoon, Undated (Oversized 34, Folder 13)
    - Tissues of Parts, Prologue, Act I Scene I Cello, Undated (Oversized 34, Folder 14)
    - Tissues of Parts, Prologue, Act I Scene I English Horn, Undated (Oversized 34, Folder 15)
    - Tissues of Parts, Prologue, Act I Scene I Harp, Undated (Oversized 34, Folder 16)
    - Tissues of Parts, Prologue, Act I Scene I Oboes, Undated (Oversized 34, Folder 17)
    - Tissues of Parts, Prologue, Act I Scene I Viola, Undated (Oversized 34, Folder 18)
    - Tissues of Parts, Prologue-Epilogue Violin 1, Undated (Oversized 34, Folder 19)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act I Flute, Undated (Oversized 34, Folder 20)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act I Scenes II-IV Bass, Undated (Oversized 34, Folder 21)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act I Scenes II-IV Bassoons 1-3 and Contra Bassoon, Undated (Oversized 34, Folder 22)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act I Scenes II-IV Cello, Undated (Oversized 34, Folder 23)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act I Scenes II-IV Clarinet and Bass Clarinet, Undated (Oversized 34, Folder 24)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act I Scenes II-III Harp, Undated (Oversized 34, Folder 25)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act I Scenes II-IV Horns 1 and 3, Undated (Oversized 35, Folder 1)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act I Scenes II-IV Oboes 1-3 and English Horn, Undated (Oversized 35, Folder 2)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act I Scenes II-IV Percussion and Timpani, Undated (Oversized 35, Folder 3)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act I Scenes II-IV Trombones 1-3 and Tuba, Undated (Oversized 35, Folder 4)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act I Scenes II-IV Trumpets 1-4, Undated (Oversized 35, Folder 5)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act I Scenes II-IV Viola, Undated (Oversized 35, Folder 6)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act I Scene III Trombones 1-3 and Tuba, Undated (Oversized 35, Folder 7)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act II Scene I Trombones 1-3 and Tuba, Undated (Oversized 35, Folder 8)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act II Scene I and II Harps 1 and 2, Undated (Oversized 35, Folder 9)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act II Scene I-III Bass, Undated (Oversized 35, Folder 10)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act II Scene I-III Bassoons 1-3 and Contra Bassoon, Undated (Oversized 35, Folder 11)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act II Scene I-III Cello, Undated (Oversized 35, Folder 12)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act II Scene I-III Clarinets 1-3 and Bass Clarinet, Undated (Oversized 35, Folder 13)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act II Scene I-III Flute 1, 2 and Piccolo, Undated (Oversized 35, Folder 14)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act II Scene I-III Horns 1-4, Undated (Oversized 35, Folder 15)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act II Scene I-III Oboes 1-3 and English Horn, Undated (Oversized 35, Folder 16)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act II Scene I-III Percussion, Undated (Oversized 35, Folder 17)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act II Scenes I-III Trumpets 1-4, Undated (Oversized 35, Folder 18)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act II Scenes I-III Viola, Undated (Oversized 35, Folder 19)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act II Scenes I-III Violin 2, Undated (Oversized 35, Folder 20)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act II Scenes II-III Trombones 1-3 and Tuba, Undated (Oversized 35, Folder 21)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act II Scene IV Bass, Undated (Oversized 35, Folder 22)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act II Scene IV Bassoons 1, 2 and Contra Bassoon, Undated (Oversized 35, Folder 23)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act II Scene IV Clarinets 1-3 and Contra Bassoon, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 1)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act II Scene IV Flutes 1 and 2, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 2)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act II Scene IV Horns 1-4, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 3)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act II Scene IV Oboes 1, 2 and English Horn, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 4)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act II Scene IV Percussion, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 5)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act II Scene IV Trombones 1-3 and Tuba, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 6)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act II Scene IV Trumpets 1-4, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 7)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act II Scene IV Viola, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 8)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act II Scene IV Violin 2, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 9)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act III Scenes I-III Bass, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 10)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act III Scenes I-III Bassoon 1 and 2, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 11)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act III Scenes I-III Bassoon 3 and Contra Bassoon, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 12)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act III Scenes I-III Cello, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 13)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act III Scenes I-III Clarinets 1-3 and Bass Clarinet, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 14)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act III Scenes I-III English Horn, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 15)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act III Scenes I-III Flutes 1, 2 and Piccolo, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 16)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act III Scenes I-III Harps, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 17)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act III Scenes I-III Horns 1 and 2, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 18)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act III Scenes I-III Horns 3 and 4, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 19)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act III Scenes I-III Oboes 1-3, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 20)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act III Scenes I-III Percussion and Timpani, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 21)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act III Scenes I-III Trombones 1 and 2, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 22)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act III Scenes I-III Trombone 3 and Tuba, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 23)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act III Scenes I-III Trumpets, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 24)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act III Scenes I-III Viola, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 25)
    - Tissues of Parts, Act III Scenes I-III Violin 2, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 26)
    - Tissues of Parts, Epilogue Bass, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 27)
    - Tissues of Parts, Epilogue Bassoons 1-3 and Contra Bassoon, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 28)
    - Tissues of Parts, Epilogue Cello, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 29)
    - Tissues of Parts, Epilogue Clarinets 1-3 and Bass Clarinet, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 30)
    - Tissues of Parts, Epilogue Flutes 1 and 2, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 31)
    - Tissues of Parts, Epilogue Harps, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 32)
    - Tissues of Parts, Epilogue Horns 1-4, Undated (Oversized 36, Folder 33)
    - Tissues of Parts, Epilogue Oboes and English Horn, Undated (Oversized 37, Folder 1)
    - Tissues of Parts, Epilogue Percussion, Undated (Oversized 37, Folder 2)
    - Tissues of Parts, Epilogue Trombones 1-3 and Tuba, Undated (Oversized 37, Folder 3)
    - Tissues of Parts, Epilogue Trumpets 1-4, Undated (Oversized 37, Folder 4)
    - Tissues of Parts, Epilogue Viola, Undated (Oversized 37, Folder 5)
    - Tissues of Parts, Epilogue Violin 2, Undated (Oversized 37, Folder 6)
    - Tissues of Parts, Epilogue Violin 2, Undated (Oversized 37, Folder 6)
    - Tissues of Vocal Parts, Prologue, Undated (Oversized 37, Folder 7)
    - Tissues of Vocal Parts, Act I Scene I, Undated (Oversized 37, Folder 8)
    - Tissues of Vocal Parts, Act I Scene II, Undated (Oversized 37, Folder 9)
    - Tissues of Vocal Parts, Act I Scene III, Undated (Oversized 37, Folder 10)
    - Tissues of Vocal Parts, Act I Scene IV, Undated (Oversized 37, Folder 11)
    - Tissues of Vocal Parts, Act II Scene I, Undated (Oversized 37, Folder 12)
    - Tissues of Vocal Parts, Act II Scene II, Undated (Oversized 37, Folder 13)
    - Tissues of Vocal Parts, Act II Scene III, Undated (Oversized 37, Folder 14)
    - Tissues of Vocal Parts, Act II Scene IV, Undated (Oversized 37, Folder 15)
    - Tissues of Vocal Parts, Act III Scene I, Undated (Oversized 37, Folder 16)
    - Tissues of Vocal Parts, Act III Scene II, Undated (Oversized 37, Folder 17)
    - Tissues of Vocal Parts, Act III Scene III, Undated (Oversized 37, Folder 18)
    - Tissues of Vocal Parts, Epilogue, Undated (Oversized 37, Folder 19)
  - The Passion of Mother Ann, 1985-1986; Undated; 4.4
    - Part I, Piano-Vocal Score, 1986 (Oversized 44, Folder 2)
    - Part I, Orchestral Score, 1986 (Oversized 44, Folder 3)
    - Part I, Orchestral Score, 1986 (Oversized 44, Folder 4)
    - Prologue and Part I, Libretto, 1985-1986 (Box 6 (4-Operas), Folder 12)
    - Prologue and Act I, Orchestral Parts, Bassoons 1 and 2, Undated (Box 6 (4-Operas), Folder 13)
    - Prologue and Act I, Orchestral Parts, Cello, 1986 (Box 7 (4-Operas), Folder 1)
    - Prologue and Act I, Orchestral Parts, Clarinet, 1986 (Box 7 (4-Operas), Folder 2)
    - Prologue and Act I, Orchestral Parts, Contra Bassoon, Undated (Box 7 (4-Operas), Folder 3)
    - Prologue and Act I, Orchestral Parts, Flutes 1 and 2, Undated (Box 7 (4-Operas), Folder 4)
    - Prologue and Act I, Orchestral Parts, Horns 1 and 2, Undated (Box 7 (4-Operas), Folder 5)
    - Prologue and Act I, Orchestral Parts, Oboes 1 and 2, Undated (Box 7 (4-Operas), Folder 6)
    - Prologue and Act I, Orchestral Parts, Percussion, Undated (Box 7 (4-Operas), Folder 7)
    - Prologue and Act I, Orchestral Parts, Trumpet, Undated (Box 7 (4-Operas), Folder 8)
    - Prologue and Act I, Orchestral Parts, Viola, 1986 (Box 7 (4-Operas), Folder 9)
    - Prologue and Act I, Orchestral Parts, Violin I, Undated (Box 7 (4-Operas), Folder 10)
    - Prologue and Act I, Orchestral Parts, Violin II, Undated (Box 7 (4-Operas), Folder 11)
    - Prologue and Act I, Piano and Vocal Score, 1986 (Box 7 (4-Operas), Folder 12)
    - Prologue, Piano-Vocal Score, 1986 (Oversized 44, Folder 1)
  - Professor Lookalike and the Children, 1987-1988; Undated; 4.5
    - Fragment of Piano-Vocal Score, Undated (Box 7 (4-Operas), Folder 13)
    - Fragment of Liberetto, Undated (Box 7 (4-Operas), Folder 14)
    - Manuscript Liberetto, 1987 (Box 7 (4-Operas), Folder 15)
    - Original Orchestral Score, p. 1-72, 1988 (Oversized 44, Folder 7)
    - Original Orchestral Score, p. 73-149, 1988 (Oversized 44, Folder 8)
    - Piano-Vocal Score with Notes, 1987 (Box 7 (4-Operas), Folder 16)
    - Script, 1987 (Box 7 (4-Operas), Folder 17)
    - Vocal Score, Original Manuscript, 1987 (Oversized 44, Folder 5)
    - Vocal Score, Copy with Notes, 1988 (Oversized 44, Folder 6)
- Screenplays, 1975; 1991; Undated; 5; 0.80 cubic ft.
  This series contains manuscripts for the multiple screenplays that Kastle wrote during his lifetime. As previously stated, some were produced while others were not. This series contains both handwritten drafts and typed manuscripts.
  - Change of Heart, Draft Version 1, 1975 (Box 1 (5-Screenplays), Folder 1)
  - Change of Heart, Draft Version 2, 1975 (Box 1 (5-Screenplays), Folder 2-3)
  - Change of Heart, Notes, Undated (Box 1 (5-Screenplays), Folder 4)
  - Change of Heart, Typed Screenplay, Undated (Box 1 (5-Screenplays), Folder 5-6)
  - The Honeymoon Killers, Copy of Manuscript, Undated (Box 1 (5-Screenplays), Folder 7-8)
  - The Honeymoon Killers Manuscript, Undated (Box 2 (5-Screenplays), Folder 1-2)
  - The Honeymoon Killers, Undated (Film 1-6)
  - The Honeymoon Killers, Undated (Dvd 1)
  - Shakespeare's Dog Manuscript, Undated (Box 2 (5-Screenplays), Folder 3-4)
  - Shakespeare's Dog Typed Screenplay, 1991 (Box 1 (5-Screenplays), Folder 5)
  - Teddy Bear Screenplay, Undated (Box 1 (5-Screenplays), Folder 6)
  - Wedding at Cana Manuscript, Undated (Box 1 (5-Screenplays), Folder 7)
  - Wedding at Cana Typed Screenplay, Undated (Box 2 (5-Screenplays), Folder 8)
- Biographical Material, 1944-1996; Undated; 6; 0.20 cubic ft.
  Series 6 contains a wide array of material pertaining to Kastle's personal life. This series contains material from Kastle's high school years, including his dipolma and a class photo. Personal and professional correspondence is also found in this series.
  - The Autographs of the Masters with inscription by Paul Wittgenstein, 1944 (Box 1 (6-Biographical Material), Folder 1)
  - Class Photographs of William Wilson Jr. High School, Undated (Box 1 (6-Biographical Material), Folder 2)
  - Commencement Programs and High School Diploma, 1945; 1948 (Box 1 (6-Biographical Material), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Professional and Personal, 1959-1960; 1996 (Box 1 (6-Biographical Material), Folder 4)
  - Engraved Plate as a Token of Appreciation from St. Peter's Church in Albany, Undated (Oversized 45)
  - Event Programs, 1946; 1950; Undated (Box 1 (6-Biographical Material), Folder 5)
  - The Voice Article about Leonard Kastle, 1986 (Box 1 (6-Biographical Material), Folder 6)
- Music Catalog, Undated; 7; 2 cubic ft. (Box 1, Box 2)
  Leonard Kastle's card catalog of music.